prodirectselect.com 2019-04-27

# Pro:Direct Select - Privacy

**Privacy Policy  
Please read all of the following information carefully.  
By using our Site and/or registering with us, you are agreeing to the terms of this Policy.**

Pro:Direct Sport Ltd are committed to protecting and respecting any personal information that you provide to us.  
Your privacy as our customer is very important to us. 

We aim to always respect your data protection rights in compliance with the latest Data Protection Laws.

**Who we are.**

This Website is owned and operated by Pro:Direct Sport Ltd.  
Pro:Direct Soccer, Pro:Direct Soccer Academy, Pro:Direct Basketball, Pro:Direct Cricket, Pro:Direct Rugby, Pro:Direct Running, Pro:Direct Select, Pro:Direct Tennis, Pro:Direct Fit, do Sport Live and Pantofola d'Oro are subsidiaries of Pro:Direct Sport Ltd

Pro:Direct Sport Ltd is registered as a data controller with the Office of the Information Commissioner under reference number ZA302607.

This Policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. 

Our Data Protection Officer (DPO).  
can be contacted by email [dpo@prodirectsport.net](mailto:dpo@prodirectsport.net)

**Personal Information We Collect**

When you visit our Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, which websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as Device Information.

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- Cookies are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [https://www.allaboutcookies.org.](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

\- Log files track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages and date/time stamps.

\- Web beacons, tags and pixels are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

We may use third party apps like WhatsApp to contact you with marketing content. We will only contact you when you have added our campaign mobile number to your WhatsApp account, and will not share this information with any other parties. Here are the privacy policies from WhatsApp.   
<https://www.whatsapp.com/legal/?eea=1#privacy-policy-how-the-general-data-protection-regulation-applies-to-our-european-region-users>

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address and phone number. We refer to this information as 'Order Information.'  
We share your payment information with Adyen as our payment processor.  
We share your Order Information with MetaPack to enable delivery of your products.  
To improve your shopping experience we share your shopping cart information with SaleCycle.

We may also collect and process the following data about you:  
Information that you provide to us by filling in forms on or via our Site.   
This includes information provided at the time of requesting products, services or information from us;  
Information that you provide to us when you write to us (including by email);  
Information that you provide to us when we speak to you by telephone.   
We may make and keep a record of the information you share with us;  
Information that you provide to us by completing surveys;  
Details of transactions you carry out through our Site including the fulfilment of your orders;  
Details of your visits to our Site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access, or information obtained by us from third parties in accordance with the Act.

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfil any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
Communicate with you; screen our orders for potential risk or fraud, and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

**Storage of your Data**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination inside or outside the European Economic Area (EEA). It may also be processed by staff operating inside or outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your orders, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing and/or processing. We will take such steps as we consider reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us via email or our Site is stored on our secure servers.  
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.  
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site, any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.  
Uses made of the information

**Aggregated Statistics**

Google Analytics is used by Pro:Direct Sport Ltd to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns across our websites.   
We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical (non-personal) data about a user's browsing actions and patterns.  
This information is anonymous and is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone.   
<https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/> You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

**Adverts**

We use Google Tag Manager to provide targeted adverts for products and services that we think may be of interest to you. We do this based on your site usage and across social media platforms.  
You can opt out of these services using the links below

[BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)

**Cookies**

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer ('Cookies' are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [https://www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).). Cookies, which are small text files, contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service.  
You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be to access all or parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies as soon you visit our site.

**Data Retention**

When you place an order through our Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless you ask us to delete this information.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**

We may share your personal information with carefully selected third party service providers and other organisations who provide us with support services or that help market our services. We provide these third party service providers or organisations with such information as they may be needed to allow them to perform their functions.  
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions of Website Use, to protect the rights, property, or safety of Pro:Direct Sport Ltd, our clients, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection or where we have your consent to do so.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes.  
You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by contacting [dpo@prodirectsport.net](mailto:dpo@prodirectsport.net)

**ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION**

You have the right to request access to certain information held by us about you.   
Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with Data Protection Law.   
Please contact [dpo@prodirectsport.net](mailto:dpo@prodirectsport.net)

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY** The Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personal information from them. If we discover that a child has provided us with personal information, we will use reasonable efforts to delete this information.  
If you have reason to believe we may have accidentally received personal information from a child under the age of 13, please immediately submit details through our Support page.

**Changes to our privacy policy** We may update this Policy at any time without notice. Any changes we may make to this Policy in the future will be posted on this page.  
Your continued use of our Site, following the posting of changes to this Policy, will mean that you accept these changes.
